ANITA WALDROPT

79-81 HASSARATH ROAD, CUNUPIA, 520514

868.719.5565 / 868.271.6557 / 868.486.0939

anita.waldropt@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

To deliver the best of what I have to offer.

Obstinate to be strong and credible force to the organisation. Self motivation is one of my key attributes,

Assiduous in decision making and problem solving for solutions are what make me strong in today's multifaceted world. – being that I am always ready for new experience and challenges.

Believing that nothing is impossible and striving for excellence are key attributes that drive my appetite to learn and grow as an individual.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

Managerial Administrative Assistant- Ministry National Diversity and Social Integration c/o National Museum and Art Gallery June 2014- Present (contract)

Responsibilities include: administrative and clerical support; dealing with The National Museum and Art Gallery many publics; supporting the curator, events and marketing coordinator and accounting and database administration.

Answer telephone, transfer calls, and greet visitors to the office

Perform correspondence with donors, volunteers, scholarship recipients and nonprofit organizations by email

Administrative Assistant/ Receptionist/ Concierge- Valsayn Luxury Spa Limited- December 2013- June 2014

Main Activities

Answer all incoming calls and handle caller's inquiries whenever possible. Re-direct calls as appropriate and take adequate messages when required

Respond to public inquiries; Receive, direct and relay telephone messages and fax messages

Direct clients to appropriate staff member

Assist in the planning and preparation of meetings

Maintain an adequate inventory of office supplies

Coordinate the repair and maintenance of office equipment

Greet, assist and/or direct clients

Support/Assist the Executive Director and other staff as requested

Provide administrative services for the Executive Director

Station Manager- Innovative Technologies and Services Limited (NP Chaguanas) June-September, 2013

Complete operations of the functional operations of the station. Managing staff approximately 10-15 persons. Complete Human Resource functions, including training and implementing of rules, regulations and standard protocol of the station.

Payroll of all staff

Inventory and Stock Management

Administrative Duties

Constant Communication with Managing Director

Branch Manager, Cold Stone Creamery April 19th 2011- May 13th 2013.

Manage the quotidian of the store while operating locally with accounting and operation bodies.

Ensured that payments for staff was on time and correct, and ensuring a safe working environment.

Inaugurate/ Diffuse of the store

Merchandising and Marketing of the brand

Cash out/ Deposit of Store Finances

Managing a full team of 20 Staff

Training of new staff/ employees

Inventory and Stock managing

Administrative duties at Flavorite Head Office

Continual articulation with Marketing Manager and Operation Manager.

Administrative Assistant, Sunfield Glass & Aluminium ltd. February 2010- November-2010 Supervisor Customer Service Staff

Ensuring staff training and customers order are completed.

Telemarketer

Calling on behalf of the company to promote their goods and services

Telephone Operator

Intercept calls to the company. Using switch board to transfer calls received and handled claims.

Customer Service Representative

Acknowledge customers, explained products and services that the company offers.

Administrative Assistant

Worked together with the sales team, operation team and managing director on special projects.

Sales Associate, Bijoux Caribbean Limited.

September 2009- January 2010

Assistant Team Leader

Opening and Closing of the store

Making cash deposit

Ensuring that the team worked cohesively

Sales Associate

Attend to Customers Stock taking/ inventory

Merchandise

Arranging the products to ensure customers got the best concept of the products offered.

Cashier

EDUCATION & TRAINING

George Washington University- Present – June 2016

Professional Certificate in Event Management

University of West indies- Centre Language Learning Present- December 2016

Complete course Mandarin Level 1A, 1B & 2A Beginners Course

October 2007- July 2010

Anglia Ruskin University c/o School of Accounting and Management

Diploma in Higher Education Business Management

2007/8

- o Business In Focus
- o Learning and Skills Development in Business
- o Business Environment
- Managing People, Finance & Marketing

2008/9

- Web Design for Business
- o Information systems
- o International Business
- o Managing Organizational Change
- o Principles of Human Resource and Management
- Marketing Management

2009/0

- o Ethics and Governance
- Strategic management
- Undergraduate Major Project (Dissertation)

August 25th- December 2010 CTS College of Business and Computer Science

Certificate in Event Management

Certificate in Web Design

June 29th- July 03rd 2009

Introduction Course at National Gas Company Trinidad and Tobago Ltd. **November 24th- December 4th 2008**

On The Job Training (OJT)

Life Skills Training

October 2006- June 2007 School of Accounting and Management.

Computer Operative and Business Management Skills (COBMS)

ManagementDistinctionQuantitative MethodsCreditBusiness CommunicationCreditFinancial AccountingPass

Computer Fundamentals &

Software Application Pass

June 2006- August 2006 Upper Level Educational Institute Limited

Complete Course of Study and Training in Computer Literacy

September 2006- 2012:

- Past Pupil President of Cunupia Secondary School
- Active Member on the Ministry of Education School Board (Past Pupil Representative)

Solely organized my Form 5 Graduation
Form Captain
In-House Captain
Awarded 2nd Place Inter House Public Speaking Competition
Net Ball Vice Captain
Senior/ Class Prefect
Awarded 1st Place in Dance/Drama
School Choir
Certificate of Attendance
Certificate of Excellence
Certificate in Good Citizenship (3 years)
Six (6) Caribbean Examination Council (C.X.C) passes

Caribbean Examination Council Passes 2006

INTEGRATED SCIENCE	GENERAL	THREE
PRINCIPLES OF ACCOUNTS	GENERAL	THREE
ENGLISH A	GENERAL	THREE
MATHEMATICS	GENERAL	THREE
PRINCIPLES OF BUSINESS	GENERAL	TWO
SOCIAL STUDIES	GENERAL	TWO

References available on request